[upbeat music]
[Joey] Hey, Charlie!
Time to go home, Ace.
Already? This is really sudden.
I like the place.
Really shit.
[guard] ...you do that.
[upbeat music continues]
Maybe I'll hit you up
next weekend.
I got a good feeling
about Green Bay.
Love to help you out, Joey.
But I'm out of the game.
[laughs]
Come on.
You gotta be shitting me, right?
No shit. I'm goin' clean.
Well, that's a fuckin' shame,
if there ever was one.
Guess this is goodbye.
It is.
You take care of yourself,
Charlie.
Good luck out there, eh.
I don't believe in luck.
I only believe in odds.
[upbeat music]
Yeah. I don't give a fuck
what time he says!
Gimme--gimme 30,000 on the...
I was a bookie.
Not only a good one.
I was the best in town.
It was a sixth sense.
I could tell if a quarterback
was comin' down with a cold,
just by looking at him
in a press conference.
I could tell how injured
a guy was after a hit,
just by the way
he walked off the field.
And on any given Sunday,
I knew the odds of one group
of meatheads clobberin'
another group of meatheads.
And if I liked you,
I'd give you those odds.
But if I didn't, I'd give you
the exact opposite.
Charlie, give 'em 50,000
on the Ravens for Jimmy.
A'right, I got it, plus four.
Don't worry about it.
I got you, I got you, I got you.
[Charlie] The only other guy
I knew who was as good as me,
if not better, was Felix.
My partner and best friend.
Yo, I wanna put 30,000
on the [indistinct]
[Charlie] His parents
moved here from Georgia,
without two pennies
to rub together.
And he grew up knowin'
what hard work was.
And he didn't want
any part of it.
While we were takin' bets
from high school kids
to state attorneys,
we were also placing 'em.
-Fuck me! God fuckin' damnit!
-[Charlie] Big ones.
Oh, my God,
I can't fuckin' believe it!
[Charlie] There's nothin'
like the anticipation.
That build-up, then boom!
Put your fucking hands
in the air!
[Charlie] Then it was over.
[noisy inhale]
They got us on a total
Greek salad of charges.
From illegal gambling
to drug possession,
unpaid parking tickets.
It was a mess.
But you know what they say:
When one cell door closes,
another one opens.
Sports weren't our
only bread and butter.
Me and Felix knew everything
about gambling.
There was a bet to be made,
we were right there to take it.
The thing about gambling is,
you might win sometimes.
But if you stay
at the table long enough...
-Ohh!
-[crowd cheering and clapping]
[Charlie] ...you'll always lose.
What's the word
on the street, Charlie.
Are you battin'
with that fat fuck meanie
from the fuckin' West Side?
Are you givin' him
my fucking money?
Are you, Charlie?
I was tryin'
to win it back for you.
And when you see
that little fuckin' prick Felix,
you tell him
I want my fuckin' money.
I want my fuckin' money!
You understand me?
What the fuck are they playin'?
Crazy Eights?
I don't know what the fuck
they're doin',
but I got 50 on fuckin' Jamal.
[Charlie] Felix got out
a year before me.
-I'm gonna miss you.
-Me too, buddy.
When I got out,
I couldn't even play
the lottery without someone
breathin' down my neck.
But Felix never forgot about
me.
Let's go.
[indistinct conversation]
["Check Your Devil" playing]
[singer]
♪ So, you think you're tough ♪
♪ And you're hard enough ♪♪
♪ That no pain can punish you ♪♪
Yo, Regina.
[singer]
♪ So you walk that walk... ♪♪
Charlie fucking Cons!
You're out.
Yeah, it's about
fuckin' time, right?
About fucking time!
You look good, Regina.
Thanks.
To time.
Here's to not wastin'
any more of it.
[singer]
♪ Let me be your queen! ♪♪
♪ Check your devil at the door ♪♪
Yo, Felix,
uh, wrote me a letter.
He said he dropped off
a package here for me.
Yeah. Holy shit, yeah.
He dropped it off months ago.
I completely forgot. A moment.
Bingo.
Good to see you, Charlie.
Good to see you, Regina.
[singer] ♪ Now the time has come
and the night is young ♪
♪ Are you ready for me? ♪♪
♪ Cause there ain't no money
and your act is funny ♪♪
♪ Let yourself be free ♪♪
[line rings]
-[Felix] Yeah?
-Yeah?
That's how you answer the phone,
you piece of shit?
Don't have caller ID over there?
[Felix] I knew it was you,
you fucking hard-on!
Great to hear your voice,
buddy.
-So, you got my package, right?
-Yeah, I got it.
[Felix] I'm in fuckin' Georgia.
The Homeland.
Charlie, listen.
Get your fuckin' passport
and get your ass down here.
A-S-A-P.
They don't know nothing
about fuckin' football here.
Yeah, I'm comin'.
But I gotta ask,
what the fuck
are we gonna do in Georgia?
[Felix]
Make fuckin' money, baby!
[Charlie]
I was on the next plane out.
[funky music]
[Charlie] In a year,
Felix had turned a shitstained
Georgian basement
into Atlantic City.
Well, maybe Reno.
But with my help, he wanted to
turn it into Vegas.
-What do you think?
-How'd you do all this?
What do you mean,
how'd I fuckin' do it?
I made a few phone calls,
I killed a few people.
Seriously?
No, not seriously,
fuckin' idiot!
I used the money.
What money?
The fuckin' money!
-The fan?
-Yeah, the fuckin' fan!
[Charlie] Every weekend,
we'd put away a few bucks
into somethin' we called
"the fan fund."
The idea being,
if the shit hit the fan,
we'd be covered.
We didn't trust banks,
so I took it to a place
that was a hundred times safer.
My mom's.
We're doin' great.
Business every fuckin' day.
That's why I brought you here.
-Come. Come, come, come.
-What?
I'm taking care
of a lot of people,
but it's fuckin' cool, right?
Our own fuckin' casino.
And we don't have to deal
with the fuckin' bullshit
from back home.
Well, bullshit'll come.
Trust me.
Yeah, but it's our
own fuckin' casino!
-[laughs]
-But this--
it's an underground,
illegal casino.
Obviously!
We've never done anything
that's fuckin' legal
in our life. [chuckles]
That's true.
Charlie, don't worry about it.
I got it all fuckin' covered.
Yeah, it's pretty great.
We'll have to get permits
or somethin'.
Pay off the chief of police.
No, we're not paying
anybody off.
Are you fuckin' nuts?
I'm taking care of a few people.
Let me handle all that shit,
all right? Listen.
Let's go inside and make
some fuckin' money, huh?
Let's make some fuckin' money!
I love you, buddy.
-Love you, buddy.
-Go.
[Charlie] What Felix managed
to put together in a year
was nothin' short
of unbelievable.
He was friends with everybody.
Whatever they wanted,
drinks, girls.
Felix made everyone
feel like they were VIPs.
This is Charlie, my new partner!
[Charlie] And my focus
was always on the tables.
It's all fun and games
on the outside,
but there's a lot of money
on these tables.
We have to keep everyone
smiling while we take it.
And make sure
they keep comin' back for more.
When we were runnin'
the sport books,
the philosophy was,
"You win some, you lose more."
No matter if someone
hit it big one week,
they'd always end up losin'
a lot more the next.
That old Kenny Rogers song
was no joke.
You really had to know
when to hold 'em
and know
when to fuckin' fold 'em.
If someone's
on a winning streak,
it's customary
to switch out the dealer.
In order to keep
the winning streak in check
and kill it altogether.
You take a card from the shoe,
and you burn it.
Changes the whole deck.
Some games made it feel like
the odds are in your favor.
If your number
hadn't come up yet,
it's sure to come up
eventually, right?
Wrong. It's called
the "house advantage."
Keep 'em playin' long enough,
the house always wins.
Let me see your passport.
Some guys asked for markers,
a house loan to keep 'em
playin'
and give 'em a chance
to win their money back.
Good for another 20.
I appreciate it. I really do.
Don't fuck this up.
But the markers
didn't come without a price.
[man grunting]
[keys jingle]
Listen, I'm gonna take your car.
You owe us money.
Get us our money back,
you get your car back.
Got it?
Let's go.
[Charlie] The house always wins.
[deep sigh]
Breakfast of champions.
I need a fuckin' drink.
-What is that?
-This guy's a convicted cheat.
We can't have him
dealin' blackjack.
-Franco?
-[Charlie] Yeah.
Franco's a good fuckin' guy.
We can't have him dealin'.
Charlie, I can't just
fuckin' fire the guy.
Well, have him
walk around the floor,
keep an eye on the tables,
see if he sees
anything funny goin' on.
All right.
We need more dealers.
We need to make more switches.
[funky music]
Sonia Poriz...
Porizkova.
Uh, you're Russian?
Is that a problem?
Why would that be a problem?
How'd you hear about us?
My friend is one
of your, uh, girls.
And that job
doesn't interest you?
You wanna be a dealer?
I'm not like my friend.
Listen, I don't judge.
We just hire 'em
to keep the VIPs company.
If somethin' happens
outside the casino,
we don't wanna know about it.
We don't take a cut.
Not judging.
Still not interested?
You ever, uh, dealt
in a casino before?
I've dealt cards,
but never in a casino.
I worked private games.
Private games? That's big money.
You're not gonna see
that kind of money,
on your side
of the table at least.
I gotta ask.
Why don't you still work there?
I got caught.
How are you still breathin'?
I paid another way.
Deal.
Sure.
Do you wanna win,
or do you wanna lose?
I only wanna win.
When can you start?
Don't you wanna see the cards?
I've seen enough.
Come back tonight.
We'll have a uniform for you,
and you'll have
to put your hair up.
My hair?
Yeah, you show up
in a dress like that,
no one's gonna be lookin'
at the cards.
Got it.
And I will.
See you?
[dance music]
Give him the other card.
Give him.
Aw, fuck.
You should probably hit.
Charlie, Charlie!
Come here, come here.
Guys,
this is my partner Charlie.
-Charlie, this is--
-Victor.
Victor Kovalev.
Nice to meet you, Victor.
I have heard
a lot about you, Charlie.
Well, I hope it was good.
This is my head of security,
Oleg [indistinct]
Oleg, shake the man's hand.
Havin' a good time?
The best time!
[speaks Russian]
[speaking Russian]
Good time.
Heh!
Victor was actually telling me
that he's thinking
about opening his own casino.
Really?
Some friendly competition.
It's good for business.
-Yes?
-Yeah.
Great for business.
[chuckles]
Well, uh, hope you enjoy
the rest of your night.
Uh, Felix,
can I have a word with you?
Yeah, yeah. I'll be right back.
Make sure he wins this hand.
Who the fuck is that?
He's a friend of mine, Victor.
Friend of mine, Victor.
Well, who the fuck's Victor?
He's a friend of mine.
What's the problem, Charlie?
My ma used to tell me, uh,
"Show me who your friends are,
-I'll show you who you are."
-Is there an issue here?
It's just, next time I ask you
who someone is, find out.
Find out who the fuck they are!
I got it. It's all good.
Come, let's go back.
-How did you do?
-Ah, good.
How are you doing?
No, no, no, no. No.
I said stay, not hit.
-Give it back! Now.
-You said hit.
You didn't listen to me!
I said stay!
I'm gonna need you to relax.
No, no, no, no, no!
You don't listen to me!
-She didn't listen to me!
-Calm down. Please calm down.
-What's seems to be the problem?
-I said--
sir, I don't want
any trouble here.
I just want my money back.
What happened?
He hit when he should've stayed.
-I didn't hit!
-Calm down, sir.
-Yes, you hit.
-I said stay!
-[Charlie] Calm down, sir.
-Sir! I said stay.
How much did he lose?
All of it.
We're gonna get you home safe.
-Here you go. Take the money!
-[Niko] Take the money.
Get up!
Let's go. Let's go!
Good night.
[Niko] Let's go. Come on!
Let's go.
You look beautiful
in that dress,
but why aren't you wearing
your uniform?
Hey, you're lucky
I put my hair up.
[Charlie]
In situations like this,
when all eyes are on you,
you have to come out
as a good guy.
What happened?
He lost.
-Everything?
-All of it.
Good. Fuck him.
I can't stand that fuckin' guy.
Give me just one more.
[Charlie] But in the dark,
away from any eyes...
One more hand
and I will go home.
[Niko] No more hands.
No more hands!
[Charlie] Sometimes you gotta be
the bad guy.
Hey, buddy, what's your name?
Patrick.
Listen, I'm gonna ask you
this one time.
And I want a straight answer.
Did you hit or did you stay?
[ominous music]
All right. You're welcome
back here any time,
if you bring money.
You hear me?
If you bring any more
of this bullshit,
we'll be sayin' a different kind
of goodbye out here. Got it?
Go.
[dance music]
Hey. You all right?
I'm fine.
Give me my marker.
[whispering]
We have another problem.
What? Of course we do.
Give me my marker.
[loudly] Give me my marker!
Charlie! Very good!
Please, tell this person
to give me my marker.
Why would I do that?
Felix promised me a marker.
Well, Felix isn't here.
[suspenseful music]
Charlie, I have treated you
very well.
I have been very nice guy!
[exhales]
Felix promised me a marker.
So, please give me my marker.
I don't know what Felix
promised you,
but all you're gonna get
is the fuck outta here.
-[Felix] Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-[screams]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, what's goin' on?
What's goin' on?
Shhh. Please, please.
-What happened?
-Your friend was just leavin'.
-Victor...
-I have just started.
Victor, please, please.
Out of respect for me.
I've always been good to you.
Please. Okay?
He's my best friend.
Please leave for me, okay?
-Talk to your partner.
-I will.
Before he makes
a very big mistake.
No, I know. I know.
I got it. Please. I got it!
I got it. Please.
Hey! C'mon. C'mon. C'mon.
Please.
-What the fuck was that?
-What the fuck is that?
Okay, listen. [exhales]
-Okay, he's not my friend. Okay?
-Yeah?
But you don't wanna know
who these people are. Trust me.
-He's Russian mob, you mean.
-Charlie--yes.
-So, they're Russian mob.
-Do you pay protection?
I do pay protection. But listen.
It was not easy
getting this fuckin' place
off the ground, Charlie.
Everything's fine.
I'll take care of it.
Okay? I'm sorry.
[dance music continues]
Do me a favor,
don't introduce me
to any more of your friends.
Okay. I got it.
Sorry about that.
Okay? Sorry about that.
[Charlie] I was ready
to let the whole thing go.
But it was too late.
The word on the street
was Victor's dad Dimitri
was 10 times worse than him.
As soon as word made it
to daddy's ears,
Dimitri decided to grace
-our fine establishment...
-Dimitri!
[Charlie] ...with his presence.
-[Felix] How are you, sir?
-[Dimitri] Good.
Your table is ready,
right over here.
I-I got your money
on the table already.
Thank you. Your partner is here?
Victor, how are you?
Yeah, uh, Charlie?
-Yup.
-Yeah, he's here.
Go get him.
-You want me to get him here?
-Now.
Okay. Okay.
[fingers snapping]
That's Dimitri.
He wants to see you.
The games begin.
Uh, Dimitri,
this is my partner, Charlie.
Mr. Kovalev,
it's an honor to meet you.
Please, call me Dimitri.
My son tells me you have a very
good operation going on here.
Making a lot of money.
Well, this is an opportunity
for you to make more.
Oh. [chuckles]
Is that what this is?
Now, you see Georgia
is not Brooklyn, Mr. Cons.
Georgia is my city.
You cannot open a bakery
without paying me my protection.
[guffaws]
Sounds a lot like Brooklyn!
And you and your friend...
you're tourists.
But you have good vodka.
Nostrovia!
Mm!
[speaks Russian]
Listen. This place
may not be Brooklyn,
but where I'm from,
guys like you
and your son are a dime a dozen.
I know how good my vodka is
'cause I know how good
my business is.
And that's exactly what this is.
-My business.
-Charlie.
Well, our business.
We've been paying
for your protection,
and we'll continue to pay
for your protection.
But, uh, I ever see your son
in this place again,
he's the one
that's gonna need protection!
And I'm not talkin'
Barry White boy over here!
-[Felix] Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-[Dimitri] Easy, easy. Sit down.
[speaking Russian]
Sit down.
Mr. Dimitri, I apologize.
Sometimes Charlie gets
a little hot headed.
Doesn't mean what he's saying.
It's fine.
I think now we go for double.
-Double? Yeah, no problem!
-[Dimitri] You pay double now.
-[Felix] We'll pay double.
-This is good.
I will forgive you
this time, Charlie.
You're new here.
I give you time to adjust
to our customs.
You know,
it's different from Brooklyn.
[shouts in Russian]
If you ever disrespect me again,
Charlie, what you will pay
will not be not with money.
[shouting in Russian]
Double.
[deep sighs]
The fuck are you doing?
-What? The fuckin' money?
-Are you fucking crazy?
Can't let these guys
push you around. That's it!
Charlie, you don't know who
the fuck you're dealing with.
They'll fucking burn
the casino down!
I don't care!
After I spent time in the joint,
I got no fucks to give!
Listen. You're the only thing
that matters to me.
You, my mom, and this casino!
Charlie, Charlie...
You can't let 'em
push you around.
You gotta show 'em strength.
I don't care
if they fuckin' kill me, Felix.
I honestly don't.
Need a fuckin' drink.
[Charlie]
With the Russians on our asses,
we took a big hit every month
that needed to be replaced.
So, these old dogs went back
to their old tricks.
We opened the books.
While the casino
was pullin' its weight,
me and Felix were pullin'
in ridiculous numbers
on everything
from football to cricket.
Oooooh!
[Charlie] You watch enough
games of anything,
and you start to see
the sway of the momentum.
[clapping and shouting]
[Charlie] You can almost fool
yourself into believing
there's a pattern to
everything.
And that's a dangerous
place to be.
-What the fuck am I looking at?
-One, US two.
Uh, it's cricket.
It's one of the most
popular games in the world.
Do you know how many people
are in India?
-Cricket?
-Cricket, man.
I'm tellin' you,
don't sleep on cricket.
That's all we got goin' here?
Yeah. I think there's gonna
be a huge upset. You do?
All right. I'm in.
What do you think?
[cricket announcer
speaking indistinctly]
[Charlie] I don't know.
Okay.
All right. I'm gonna go
give this to Joey.
All right, buddy.
[continue speaking indistinctly]
Whoa! Did you see that?
-[Felix] What, what, what, what?
-Did you see that?
Whoa. Did you see this?
Come here, come here!
C'mere, c'mere, c'mere, c'mere!
[Felix] What, what,
what, what, what, what?
[both screaming]
-[Charlie] Did you see...
-Did we win, did we win?
Uh, well, I haven't--
the game's not over,
but we're on the way.
-Then why the fucking tell--?
-Yeah, did you see that?
Did you see that catch?
Charlie, shut the fuck up!
[Charlie] It was like
taking money from a baby.
Hey, can I walk you home?
I'm not going home.
Well, where are you goin'?
To a game.
Okay, well,
can I walk you to the game?
No.
Why not?
Because I'm not walking there.
Well, good.
I've got some money for you.
Okay, great.
[gentle piano music]
Are you sure this is the place?
Yeah. You're coming?
Let's go.
[Charlie] Cynthia ran
these underground poker games
every week with lots of cash
and very little trouble.
There was a rumor
that she was a vampire,
because nobody ever saw her
during the day.
Some say she was a gypsy.
I don't know what she was,
but I do know she was a pro.
You bring date tonight?
He's just a friend, Cynthia.
-Friend?
-Mm-hmm.
No play?
Hey, you playing?
Uh, no. I don't play.
He no play.
Charlie, got my money?
Yeah.
Raise.
Six hundred.
[Charlie]
The betting, the stakes,
the whole energy of the room
put me in a trance.
I am all in.
How much was it?
[dealer] Four hundred.
I'm all in.
[Charlie] Sonia was a natural.
One more kill.
[softly] You're incredible.
You have no idea.
[Charlie] Been a long time
since I've done that.
[Sonia] What's the expression?
Like riding a bicycle, right?
[laughs] I didn't mean the sex.
I meant being on
the other side of the table.
What'd you think of it?
It's dangerous.
I meant the sex.
[both laughing]
That too.
I need to go to bed.
Alone.
Okay, I get it.
-Goodnight.
-[Charlie chuckles]
[soft music]
Is everything, all right,
okay? [indistinct]
-[Mila] Yeah, I'm good.
-[Felix] [indistinct]
Take it, it's yours.
Let me get
another drink, please.
[sighs]
-Hey.
-Hey, Charlie.
This is my friend Mila.
Hi. Nice to meet you, Charlie.
Mila was just leaving.
Mila.
Who the hell is that?
Just a girl. You know.
No, I don't know.
Don't worry about it. I got it.
That usually means
I got somethin' to worry about.
Where you goin'?
[singer singing
in foreign language]
[Victor speaking Russian]
What'd I tell you, Victor?
Huh?
Charlie. How you doin'?
What'd I tell you
and your father?
You can't come in
my casino anymore!
You tell me not to go inside!
I'm not inside.
[giggles]
Well, what's she doin' in there?
Just a little side business.
Little. Very little.
Tiny actually.
[speaking Russian]
You know what's this?
[laughing]
Felix will tell you.
[singer singing
in foreign language]
Goodnight, Charlie.
Goodnight, Charlie. [laughs]
Goodnight.
I love you too, Charlie!
[laughs]
[speaking Russian]
Are you outta your fuckin' mind?
Take it easy! What happened?
What's goin' on with you, Felix?
And don't you fuckin' tell me,
"Don't worry about it!"
Charlie,
calm the fuck down, okay?
Listen.
Some people want more than
fuckin' drinks and company,
all right?
Are you selling drugs
with Victor in our casino?
It's not drugs! Calm down!
Are you selling drugs
with Victor in our casino?
It's a yes or no question.
First of all,
it's my fucking casino.
And second of all, fuck you
and that fucking high horse
you came riding on!
What's going on with you, Felix?
I'm fucking perfect!
[singer] ♪ [indistinct] ♪♪
You called me here. Remember?
You called me here!
Partners. Those were your words.
Now we got Russian mobsters
bustin' my balls.
We're not pimps!
We're not drug dealers!
We're not cheats.
This casino can handle anything.
But not if we're not
on the same page.
You know what? Fuck you!
I'm sick and tired of you
fuckin' tellin' me
that I'm always fuckin' wrong!
Look at how much fuckin' money
you're making!
Look at this fuckin' suit!
-Fuck you! Fuck you!
-It's not about money.
[door slams]
[singer] ♪ To the fire ♪♪
♪ To the flame ♪♪
♪ [indistinct] again ♪♪
♪ [indistinct] ♪♪
Charlie...
Here you go.
[sighs] Thank you.
[singer]
♪ Been [indistinct] again ♪♪
Hey. If you wanna be big
in this city,
there will always be someone
who will remind you
just how small you really are.
I asked for your advice once,
you don't have
to keep givin' it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[phone buzzes]
-Yeah?
-[Victor] Hello.
-What do you want?
-[Victor] I have Felix.
-What happened, Char--
-Where's Felix?
Charlie? Charlie!
[tires screeching]
[tense music]
[Charlie] Where is he?
Where is he?
It's time for you to stop
talking and listen.
My father is
a very traditional man.
A very simple man.
A very demanding man.
But has no vision.
I, on the other hand,
have nothing but vision.
I'll be taking
my father's place very soon.
All his operation,
all his power.
I'm going to say carefully,
that I don't stutter.
The casino is mine.
And so are you!
You're crazy.
Oleg?
Felix, no!
No, no, no.
[Victor] Get him out!
[Oleg] He's alive, he's alive.
C'mon, Felix.
You okay?
[mumbles] I'm gonna kill
these motherfuckers.
[groggily] We're not fuckin'
killers, Charlie.
[Victor] Felix! Hah!
[tires screeching]
Gonna get you to the hospital.
No, no hospital.
C'mon, you can barely stand.
Think we should just fuckin' go.
Look what they did
to my fuckin' face.
No, no, we're not quittin'.
[gasps] Okay.
[Charlie] Let's get you home.
[engine revving]
-[door slams open]
-What happened?
-I can't right now.
-Charlie!
Hey. If you enjoy breathing,
I would probably take the deal.
Make nice with the Russians,
show them that you're reasonable
until you can figure out a way
to show them that you're not.
Felix is gonna be away
for a while.
I'd like you to help me run
the casino until he returns.
If that sounds like fun.
It sounds terrible.
[chuckles]
If Victor and his people are
gonna be walkin' all over us,
I need someone
who can hold their own.
Okay.
But one condition.
I'm wearing my hair down.
Deal.
[chuckles]
[tense music]
[Charlie] It didn't take long
for them to move in.
I had to do somethin'
to get my head straight.
There was only one thing
that I could think of.
I had to go see that vampire.
Be right back.
[Victor] Where is my shot? Aah!
-To casino!
-To casino.
Ah.
Listen, I'm gonna take off
early, all right?
Everything okay?
Yeah, I just need
a little time to myself.
Okay. See you tomorrow?
See you tomorrow.
But none of these assholes.
[upbeat music]
[Charlie] I needed a win. Badly.
This was the only way
I could get it.
Hey, Cynthia.
Hmm. Hello, Charlie.
Hmm. No Sonia tonight?
No Sonia.
Hmm.
You play?
I play.
[singer]
♪ She needs to [indistinct] ♪♪
Here.
Give him his chip.
Thank you.
There is one rule here, hmm?
You play, you stay. No refund.
You lose or you win,
there is not second place.
I never lose.
Hmm.
I trust you!
Not on your life.
-Good luck!
-Thank you.
The push, the pull.
The highs, the lows.
The sound of the chips.
I was back.
[singer] ♪ [indistinct] ♪♪
♪ I know she'll live with it ♪
♪ Since she was coming
to [indistinct] ♪♪
All right,
let's see what you got.
The American is here.
Looks like that's mine.
Lady Love.
800.
I'm all in.
-[door slams open]
-King of Hearts.
Huh? What are the chances?
[grunts]
[tense music]
[sighs]
[Peter] Good. Leave us.
Do you know who I am?
[Charlie]
I knew exactly who he was.
Peter Gasu was one
of the most successful
casino owners in Georgia.
If you dug
a little deeper, though,
he was as dirty as they came.
But his casinos were so clean
they squeaked.
I'm a big fan.
I'm going to take that as a yes.
Well, I also know who you are,
so we can skip
the introductions.
Are you gonna kill me?
Kill you?
Oh, maybe you just think
you know who I am then?
No.
No one is dying today.
Then what do you want?
Illegal gambling establishments
have no place in my city.
If there is any bet to be made,
big or small,
it must be under my roof.
What if they like my roof
better than they like your roof?
Oh.
The poker game
you attended earlier,
the people that ran it,
they also made jokes.
I don't like jokes.
Noted.
I'll give you two weeks
to get your affairs in order
and leave my city.
And if I don't?
Then I'll tell you a joke.
But you won't like
the punch line.
[Charlie] Say what you will
about his methods,
but this man sure knew
how to run a casino.
[Victor] Yeah.
[clapping]
[shouting in Russian]
Hey.
Hey. Feeling better?
Uh, do you know Peter Gasu?
Who doesn't?
Well, we're officially
on his radar.
If we weren't fucked before,
we are now.
Hey. Gasu is a businessman,
he's not a gangster.
I'm not sure he knows that.
[Victor] Woo-hooo! Yeah!
[Charlie] Felix!
Felix!
There he is! There he is.
Aw, how you feelin'?
Better than I look.
I'm coming down.
You gotta lock your door!
Unless you want another visit
from the Russians.
Ready to get back to work?
Yeah, I need a few more days.
We don't have a few days,
we have two weeks.
-Why, what's goin' on?
-Where'd you bring me?
I got Russian mobsters
on one ball
and Peter Gasu on the other.
Who the fuck is Peter Gasu?
Amazing!
The only person in Georgia
you don't know.
Charlie, calm the fuck down.
Have a fuckin' drink!
You're gonna have
a fuckin' heart attack!
Calm down, lemme get dressed!
I'm gonna have a heart attack,
if you keep tellin' me
to calm down!
Charlie! Calm down, we got this!
I'll be right back.
You need to get laid, Charlie!
I don't need to get laid.
[rock music]
-[Charlie] Hey.
-We got a problem.
Of course we do. Where is he?
Your office.
-The office now?
-Yeah.
[singer singing
in foreign language]
[ominous music]
Dimitri.
Make yourself comfortable.
You came alone? I'm insulted.
I like you, Charlie. Very much.
You have spirit.
It will be a challenge to break,
and I love challenges.
Now, explain please.
What's this?
Oh, that. That's, uh,
none of your business.
Well, that's what we have
to discuss.
-Business?
-Oh, you want your chair back?
I'm good.
Felix?
Felix.
I was told Victor
paid you a visit.
Tsk-tsk-tsk.
Yeah.
Showed me some
of that Russian love.
I apologize
for my son's behavior.
He takes his aggression
after his mother,
God rest her so--
[speaking Russian]
Wait. You two know each other?
I didn't recognize you
with your clothes on.
Go to Hell, Dimitri.
What do you want, Dimitri?
The more I hang out with you,
the more I miss Victor.
Talkin' about Victor.
Now you see,
Victor wants to take over
my business.
My own son wants to see me
rotting in a grave,
so he can dance all over it.
We got more in common
than I thought.
What I'm about to tell you
does not leave this room.
The only way it will
is on dead lips.
Understood?
You can nod with your head.
-Do you understand?
-We understand.
[Dimitri] Okay.
My men... [sniffs]
are shifting their loyalties
over to Victor.
As a result, other organizations
will begin doing the same.
I cannot show weakness.
I must show them that
-this is my city!
-[bangs table]
And I will do whatever it takes
to make sure it stays that way.
Capisce?
How are you gonna do that?
I cannot trust my men
to carry out what I am planning.
[praying in Russian]
I need you to kill Victor.
Uh, listen, Dimitri.
It seems like you're dealing
with a lot,
but we're not the guys
for the job.
But I'm gonna take over
the casino.
We're not killers, Dimitri.
But you have to understand.
With Victor gone,
I will cement my presence
amongst my sons,
among my people,
among my rivals.
You both will work for me.
Just, you know.
With all due respect, Dimitri,
we gotta talk about this.
Enough talk!
[tense music]
You have three days.
Dimitri. Dimitri!
[Charlie sighs]
The fuck are we gonna do now?
[mockingly] Just relax.
Don't worry!
This is not fuckin' time
to fuckin' play games, Charlie.
The fuck are we gonna do?!
I don't know.
We'll, uh, get a drink
and think about it.
I'm gonna call Joey.
Sonia!
[Sonia] I'll be right back.
[singer singing
in foreign language]
Hey.
When were you gonna tell me?
I wasn't.
You think that's a important
detail to leave out?!
What's the difference?
What else haven't you told me?
Come on, Charlie.
You're being dramatic.
Oh. I'm being dramatic?!
-Yeah.
-You've been friends
with the Russian mob
this whole time,
the Russian mob
that's tryin' to take my casino,
that's tryin' to kill me!
-And I'm being dramatic.
-Hey!
I'm not friends with them!
They're the ones who assured
I needed a cane
for the rest of my life
in order to walk two steps!
So yeah, you're being dramatic!
I put you in charge.
I trusted you.
Does this really change things?
It changes everything!
So, now what?
I don't know,
uh, Felix is back, so.
Oh.
So you don't need me anymore.
Okay.
Do you wanna know why
I didn't tell you?
It's because I didn't trust you.
That's why.
Goodbye, Charlie.
[singer singing in
foreign language]
You think maybe you're
a little too hard on her?
I gotta be hard on someone.
Yeah, but...
if she really knows these people
like she says she does,
then she can probably be
an asset. You know?
Help us deal with these people,
you know?
Explain to us
what we need to do.
Maybe you go get her.
-Go.
-Fuck.
-Sonia.
-Fuck off.
-[Charlie] Sonia.
-What?!
Listen. I'm lost.
I don't know--
I don't know what I'm doing.
Please. I need your help.
Always need my help.
[softly] Yeah.
You want my advice?
I say, get them
in a room together
and have them
turn on each other.
[pop music]
[singer] ♪ [indistinct]
I believe I [indistinct] ♪♪
[Felix] What happened?
We need to plan a party.
What are we celebrating?
New Russian partners.
We got new Russian partners?
Wow.
[Charlie]
Get to the office, all right?
For the most part,
nothin' changed at the casino.
Our clientele came to us
for hospitality.
They felt important here.
Like they were somebodies.
So, they kept comin' back.
But Victor brought
in his own clientele.
Mostly scumbags who came here
to feel the same thing.
Place was gonna be crawlin'
with those cockroaches soon.
It was only a matter of time.
[phone buzzing]
-Hello?
-[Peter] We need to talk.
We sure do.
[upbeat music]
A not so little birdie
has brought to my attention
that you're in bed
with Dimitri and his son.
They're not partners.
What are they then?
They're bullies.
I figured you could appreciate
the difference.
You've got two days, Charlie.
Two days to get your affairs
in order and leave my city.
You can relay that message
to Dimitri as well.
And please,
don't try anything stupid.
I've got all of the authorities
in my pocket.
I wouldn't dream of insulting
your intelligence, Peter.
Good.
[slow music]
What? What's goin' on,
what's goin' on?
Everything, Felix.
Everything's goin' on.
Victor's running amok
outta this fuckin' place.
-We lost two regulars already.
-Doesn't matter anyway.
This place is gonna
be ashes in two days.
Is there anything we can do,
you think?
We can drink!
Nobody wants us here.
Maybe move back to Brooklyn,
get a regular job?
What do you think?
Rather lock myself in the office
and go down with the ship.
-[door knocking]
-Yeah, you're right.
Victor wants a word.
-Now?
-Yep.
"Sabotage." That's a good word!
-We'll be right there.
-All right.
Let's go see what he wants.
-[upbeat music]
-[groans]
Gentlemen!
Do you want to drink something?
Maybe something from the menu?
Nah, we're good.
Do you know who Peter Gasu is?
Yeah, a casino owner. Of course.
A wolf! In a sheep's clothing.
Well, what does this
have to do with us?
I just want you invite him
to a party.
Uh, well, I don't think
that's a good idea.
-Yeah.
-Peter Gasu's a public figure.
Somethin' happens to him,
people are gonna notice.
It'll take the cops
all of three minutes
to figure it out
and come knockin' on your door.
Hey.
I just want to talk with him.
Right.
Get it done.
[Charlie] Everybody
wanted a piece of us.
And it wasn't because
of our dazzling personalities
and prime real estate.
They coulda just put a bullet
in our head
and taken the fuckin' casino.
But the sports booking
was bringin' in
more than $50,000 a week,
steady.
The phones in New York
were ringin' off the hook,
not to mention LA and Miami.
Killin' us would turn
too many heads
and risk dryin' up the well
for good.
-They're late.
-They'll show.
What?
We just tell him? That's it?
That's it.
-And then what?
-Then, hopefully,
they'll go
at each other's throats,
with all their family bullshit.
And we'll get a second
to breathe.
[singer] ♪ Until I've had
too much, yeah ♪♪
Then what do we do?
Then we deal with the Georgian.
What's the plan with that?
I'm workin' on it.
So, no plan. Nice.
-Here we go.
-I thought it was a party?
Ha! Why the long faces?
Awww, you don't have to say
goodbye to the casino, guys.
Just say hello to the new boss.
I will take a good care of her.
Let's party!
Well, we're still waitin'
for one more.
[Victor] Yeah?
For new beginnings!
-Nostrovia!
-[Oleg] Nostrovia.
[tense music]
Surprise! Now it's a party.
What's this?
It's an intervention.
Don't be scared.
-I've had two of 'em.
-[chuckles]
Please.
So, I thought, since
we're all gonna be spendin'
a lot more time together,
you two could bury the hatchet.
You know, patch things up?
There's nothing to patch up.
Really?
Victor, maybe you wanna start?
This party is over.
Okay. I'll start. Dimitri.
Victor doesn't only want
my business.
He wants your business too.
He's fucking with us.
Yes, but is this true?
Maybe.
I have some ideas, to expand.
And these ideas,
do they involve me?
You live in past, Father.
Old school in the New World.
My ideas is for the future.
You can join them.
With me.
But not as boss.
Bravo.
Truth finally.
-Incredible.
-[laughs]
This is good, guys.
This is--this is growth.
Uh, Dimitri, maybe you wanna
share your ideas with Victor.
You made your point, Charlie.
This changes nothing.
My son and I will settle down
our business in private.
But still,
we are taking your casino.
What ideas you talking about?
You were right, Vitka.
He is fucking with us.
Victor, uh, your dad doesn't
want you runnin' the business.
It's not only that.
He doesn't want you breathing.
-[gun cocks]
-Holy shit.
I want the truth.
-Now.
-They don't belong to our world.
Did you give the order?
[dramatic music]
Papa, did you give the order?
-[gunshot]
-[woman screams]
[gasps] What the fuck?
Papa. Papa!
Papa.
Well, he's dead.
Take him to the car.
What have you think
is gonna happen?
I don't know.
Exchange of words, maybe a hug.
Not an exchange bullets?
No. I didn't. But you--
were both pushin' us!
We're just tryin' to buy
some time.
[laughing]
Time is something
you cannot buy, Charlie.
Yeah.
[suspenseful music]
Ah!
Let's go.
[suspenseful music]
Victor, where are you taking us?
Don't talk.
Look, we're just gonna go back
to New York. Please.
You want to go home?
Yeah.
I'll take you home. [laughs]
[suspenseful music]
[speaking Russian]
[sighs heavily]
My mother...
hated my father.
She would tell me
stories about him
when I was a child
that I never believed.
So, I thought: she just saying
things to hurt him.
To turn me against him!
[laughing]
Papachka!
Papa!
[speaks Russian]
[thuds]
[spits]
As I got older,
I found out
that the stories were all true.
You...
work for me now.
You need more time?
There is plenty of room
out here...
for two more holes!
[laughing]
And you can have
all the time in the world.
To the car, nyet?
[car engine starts]
[men speaking foreign language]
[tense music]
[Charlie]
I couldn't see straight.
I was missin' something.
I needed help,
a different perspective.
[knock on door]
It's open.
[door closes]
Victor killed his father.
-What?
-Fuck it!
He deserved it,
after what he did to you.
What would you do
if you were me?
I would stay small.
[Charlie] Excuse me! Mr. Gasu?
-Uh, hi.
-Come to say goodbye?
Actually, I wanted to invite you
to a farewell party.
I don't like parties.
The Russians'll be there.
Okay. Come to my office.
Take a seat, Charlie.
The Russians wanna sit down.
Discuss terms.
You're their errand boy now?
They didn't give me
much of a choice.
You can go tell the Russians
that the casino will burn,
no matter who owns it.
They're not gonna like that.
I'm not expecting them to.
Well, the party
is still gonna happen.
But I've got a proposition
of my own.
I'm late for my meeting.
Just give me two minutes...
and you'll have
a better understanding.
We can have a proper goodbye.
You have 60 seconds.
[sighs]
-He's coming.
-Nice.
[slow upbeat music]
Thanks for comin'.
I think you should
just walk away.
Too late.
[singer singing
in foreign language]
Why did you listen to me?
Because you make sense.
If it fails,
you're both dead men.
If we don't try,
we're dead anyway.
Gonna miss you, Charlie.
Let's save the goodbyes, okay?
Unless it's a goodbye kiss.
Here.
[singer singing
in foreign language]
[keypad beeping]
[line rings]
-[Victor] Hello.
-Victor.
-You on your way?
-[Victor] Yes.
Good.
I've got good news for you.
-[Victor] I will be there soon.
-All right.
We'll see you soon.
-[sighs]
-Did you call him?
-Yeah.
-Is he coming?
-Okay, good.
What did Sonia want?
She wanted to talk me out of it.
Smart girl.
Yeah.
Sometimes the smartest choices
are the ones
that get you killed.
That makes no sense.
Well, what's smart? Givin' up?
It's not about giving up.
It's about breathing
for a few more years.
And then what?
Just let them win?
It's not about
winning or losing.
It's about survival.
All right. Then go survive.
Go ahead.
No one's stoppin' you.
You can go.
Not that smart.
Neither am I.
[laughs]
There's somethin'
I didn't tell you
about my conversation
with Peter Gasu.
I don't like the sound
of that, Charlie.
Ah. You're early.
Gentlemen!
I'm excited to hear your offer.
All right.
-Ahhh!
-Well...
we want to offer you the casino.
And sell it to you,
under two conditions.
Two conditions? I'm shocked.
One, you keep me and Felix
on the payroll
but off the books.
Off the books?
Yeah. As if we never existed.
We don't want any part
of your side hustles.
Just casino work. All right?
Off the books.
I have better idea.
What about...
I just fucking
take the casino...
put you both... [giggles]
in the hole next to my father
and you could be
off the books permanently.
Well, that would
just be stupid, Victor.
[laughs] Y'know?
I mean, why would you do that?
We got all this money
flowin' in from Los Angeles,
Miami, New York, Vegas...
and that would all dry up.
It's just bad business.
[laughing] I'll keep you around.
You make me laugh.
[laughter]
Funny guy, this guy.
Ah?
So, what's the second thing?
Like you asked,
Peter Gasu is comin' here.
Tomorrow night.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
You should've started with that.
I wanted to surprise you.
Listen, I don't want any blood
in Felix's casino, Victor.
This is my casino. Remember?
Yeah, yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow night.
See you tomorrow, boss!
Boss!
Come on.
[singer singing
in foreign language]
So, what do you think?
I didn't have to use this, so...
that's good.
But I wanted to.
So, what didn't you tell me
about the Gasu thing?
[chuckles]
[dramatic music]
[Charlie] Sonia was right.
I shoulda just walked away.
But I needed to see her
one more time.
If anyone knows how to handle
these Slavic fucks, it's her.
Sonia.
Sonia?
Sonia! Sonia!
[gasping] It's all right.
-[coughing]
-Sonia.
Made you some tea.
Thanks.
Careful, it's hot.
You okay?
I think the answer
to that is obvious, no?
I don't--I don't wanna pry.
I'm in pain all the time.
If I don't take pills,
the pain comes back.
[Charlie] I get it.
It's all right.
Look...
I wasn't trying
to do anything, okay?
It was an accident.
I get it.
I'll let you
get some sleep, okay?
Can you stay?
Sure.
[dramatic music]
[Charlie] This was it, game day.
I didn't like the odds,
but I've been wrong before.
I was hoping that this
was one of those times.
I'm gonna miss this place.
Yeah. Me too.
Uh, maybe someday you'll get
your own office, buddy.
Yeah.
Actually, that makes it
all worth it, right?
[laughs]
Fuck it.
We did what we can, right?
[soft rock music]
[Oleg sniffles, groans]
-[speaking Russian]
[speaking Russian]
Here.
I'm gonna get dressed.
Be ready in 20 minutes.
Yes?
[beeps]
Get the car ready.
[tense music]
[car engine starts]
[dog barking on a distance]
So weird when it's empty, huh?
You ready for this?
-No. You?
-Nope.
Victor.
An empty casino,
it's a bad sign.
Yeah, well, we couldn't
have clients here,
in case you decide to show Peter
the same courtesy
you showed your father.
Charlie, I'm hurt.
You think that little of me?
You're a dangerous man, Victor.
A real man. A strong man.
Yeah, c'mon. Sit down, relax.
Don't tell me "relax."
Some things are universal.
How 'bout a drink, all right?
I got a special bottle.
From my own personal stash.
-Yeah?
-The best!
It--it's in the...
Yeah. We'll get it.
We'll be right back, all right?
Come on, c'mon.
-Come on.
-[Felix] Okay.
We need to get him
to that office.
How much time do we have?
Uh, 10 minutes.
Stay here.
Hey!
Where are you going?
Uh, get you the...
-special bottle.
-The vodka.
You go...
you stay.
All right. Okay.
I'm thirsty. Go.
See you later.
We have much to discuss.
Come on.
What time is he coming?
Uh, he should be here
any minute now, actually.
[suspenseful music]
He's late on purpose.
He's sending the message.
Uh...
You look tense, Charlie.
I'm just wondering
where Felix is with that booze?
I could really
use a drink right now.
I left him at the casino
with Victor.
And his guys.
All right, I'll call you.
I'll call you.
Okay, I'm waiting outside.
Okay, bye.
[suspenseful music]
You trust him?
Who, Felix?
With my life.
Good.
Very good.
Trust is very important.
Yeah.
You trust me?
Is that a trick question?
Answer it and find out.
Sure, I trust you.
You're smart.
You're a visionary.
I was going
to shoot you tonight.
You and your partner. Felix.
Well, your use of the past tense
is reassuring.
Trust is very important.
You didn't trust me?
No.
What about now?
You're still alive. So yes!
[laughs]
Glad you came to that decision
before you started drinking.
You trust Peter?
Is this another trick question?
No tricks.
You say yes,
I put the gun away.
You say no,
Peter will join
my father tonight.
Yes, I trust Peter.
He's a money guy.
That's all he cares about.
You guys are gonna make
a lot of money together.
-Okie dokie! Yeah!
-Okay.
-I'm thirsty.
-Yeah, you know what?
I got an incredible bottle
in my office.
I can get that for you,
all right?
-The best.
Go, go.
I'll be right back.
Wait here, look.
[tense music]
So, what didn't you tell me
about the Gasu thing?
-I made us a deal.
-What kind of deal?
[Charlie]
The first thing you gotta do
is get the money
out of the safe.
You have 60 seconds.
Dimitri's dead.
-Victor killed him.
-[Peter] How do you know?
[Charlie] I was at the party.
And that's why he wants
to throw a party for you.
[Peter]
Why are you telling me this?
You're as good as dead.
If I don't kill you,
Victor will.
I'm out of time
and out of options.
Victor's a lunatic gangster,
and you're a smart,
I hope, businessman.
That's why I wanna make you
a business proposal.
You have 30 more seconds.
[speaking Russian]
[suspenseful music]
We'll bring you
all of our clients.
Every single one of 'em.
And these aren't tourists.
We're talkin' big money.
Repeat numbers.
What's in it for you?
Jobs.
You hire us, strictly legit.
And we work for you,
doin' what we do best.
[speaking Russian]
We're not gangsters, Peter.
We're gamblers.
You're proposing
quite the gamble.
Yeah, well,
what have I got to lose?
[suspenseful music]
[speaks Russian]
[gunshots]
[suspenseful music]
[honking]
[dog barking]
[Felix]
Charlie, Charlie! Come here!
Get in the car!
Get in here, get in here!
[Charlie laughs]
[Felix]
Get in here, get in here!
-Did you get the money?
-Yeah, I got the money!
Get in, get in, get in!
[laughs]
We did it, bro.
We fucking got it.
-We did it.
-Let's get outta here.
Get outta here.
We can start another fan fund!
[soft upbeat music]
[Charlie] It took us
less than six months
to triple Peter's business.
We eventually became partners.
Felix always knew
what people needed,
even before they did.
He became
the head of hospitality.
Growin' up, I idolized
the biggest
casino owners in Vegas.
Guys who made big moves
and had Vegas
at their fingertips.
I woulda never imagined
that I'd be standin'
in my own casino one day.
I definitely never thought
I'd be workin'
with people
I cared so much about.
What are the odds?
[dramatic music]
[Charlie] For a guy
that doesn't believe in luck...
I was pretty fuckin' lucky.
[singer]
♪ I've been getting tired ♪
♪ So tired
of this mess we're in ♪
♪ I needed to express ♪
♪ It's been
a trying time for me ♪♪
♪ I've been getting over ♪
♪ So over this dystopia ♪
♪ I'm getting claustrophobia ♪
♪ I need some space to breathe ♪♪
♪ I am on your side ♪
♪ But we can't hide ♪♪
♪ We've lost
this round tonight ♪♪
♪ Don't always try
the best I can ♪
♪ And want to hand it
in sometimes ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess ♪
♪ Fuck this mess ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess we're in ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess ♪
♪ Fuck this mess, oh ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess we're in ♪♪
♪ I can't cut the words out ♪
♪ And shove them back
inside my mouth ♪
♪ I knew this night
was going south ♪
♪ I heard it in my tone ♪♪
♪ I am on your side ♪
♪ But we can't hide ♪♪
♪ We've lost
this round tonight ♪♪
♪ Don't always try
the best I can ♪
♪ And want to hand it
in sometimes ♪♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Fuck this mess ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess we're in ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess ♪
♪ Fuck this mess, oh ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess we're in ♪♪
♪ Fuck this mess ♪
♪ Fuck this mess ♪♪